

MCA with 4.6 experience in software development



Current Designation: Senior Software Engineer Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 8 Month(s)

Current Company: Taliun Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Sr. Software Engineer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Requirement

Analysis, Solution Architecture, C#, VB, ASP. NET MVC, SQL Server, MySQL, MS

Access, JQuery, JavaScript, CSS, HTML, Project Management

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Modified: 19-Jan-21 Last Active: 19-Jan-21

Summary

4.6 years of experience in analysis, design and development of client/server, web based application. Expertise in developing web applications in Microsoft Visual Studio 2015 using ASP.Net (MVC), C#, SQL Server 2014. Experience in developing windows applications in Visual Studio Code using React and Electron Experience in developing web applications in Visual Studio Code using React and Node Strong communication and client interaction skills.

Effective in working independently and collaboratively in teams.

Work Experience

Taliun as Senior Software Engineer Nov 2020 to Till Date

Thinkitive Technologies Pvt Ltd as Sr. Software Engineer - .Net Aug 2018 to Oct 2020

Omni-Bridge System Pvt Ltd as Software Engineer Jan 2016 to Jul 2018

Education

UG: B.Sc (Computers) from North Maharashtra University (NMU) in 2013

PG: MCA (Computers) from North Maharashtra University (NMU) in 2015

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version La	ast Used	Experience
C#,VB			
ASP.Net (MVC)			
SQL Server			
MySQL, MS Access			
Window 2003/XP/7/8/10			
Red Hat Linux			
IIS6.0, IIS7.0			
jQuery, JavaScript			
.Net ,React, Electron, CSS, HTML			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Hindi	Expert			
Marathi	Expert			

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time